Guide to the New-York Historical Society Geographic Images Collection circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: New York City Views - Manhattan
  - Subseries IA: MANHATTAN - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Street Views
      - Elizabeth Street (East Bayard Farm) (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Elm Street (See also Lafayette Street) (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Essex Street (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Exchange Place (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Extra Place (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Ferry Street (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Forsyth Street (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Fort Washington Avenue (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Frankfort Street (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Franklin Square (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Franklin Street (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Front Street (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Fulton Street (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Gay Street (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Gold Street (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Gouverneur Street (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Gramercy Park (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Great Jones Street (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Greene Street (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Greenwich Avenue (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Greenwich Street (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Grove Court and Grove Street (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Hague Street (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Hamilton Place and Hamilton Terrace (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Hanover Square (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Harrison Street (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Haven Avenue (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Henderson Place (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Henry Street (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Herald Square (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Hester Street (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Hillside Avenue (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Horatio Street (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Houston Street (West Houston Street) (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Howard Street (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Hubert Street (Trinity Church Farm) (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Hudson Street (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Irving Place (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Jackson Street (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Jacob Street (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Jacobus Place (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - James Slip and James Street (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Jane Street (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - John Street (see also Burling Slip) (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Jones Street (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - King Street (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Lafayette Court (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Lafayette Place (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Lafayette Street (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Laight Street (Trinity Church Farm) (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Lenox Avenue (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Leonard Street (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Leroy Street (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Lewis Street (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Lexington Avenue (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Liberty Place (formerly Green Street) (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Liberty Street (Crown street 18th century) (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Place (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Lispenard Street (Calkhook farm) (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - MacDougal Alley (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - MacDougal Street (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Madison Avenue (23rd street to 27th street) (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Madison Avenue (27th street to 34th street) (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Madison Avenue (34th street to 45th street) (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Madison Avenue (45th to 72nd street) (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Madison Avenue (72nd to Harlem River) (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Madison Street (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Maiden Lane (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Mail Street (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Manhattan Avenue (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Manhattan Street (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Marble Hill Avenue (former Kingsbridge avenue) (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Market Street (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Mercer Street (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Milligan Place (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Minetta Lane and Minetta Street (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Mitchell Place (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Monroe Street (original Lombardy street) (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Moore street (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Morningside Avenue (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Morton Street (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Mott Street (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Mott's Lane (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Mulberry Street (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Mulberry Bend-GLASS NEGATIVE- Special access (Box 21, Folder 20.5)
        Glass negative of women selling corn on Mulberry Bend. Negative is in two parts: the image, and the frame around it with the publisher's information: "T.H.McAllister, manufacturing optician."
        Conditions Governing Access
        Please see librarian for access.
      - Murray Street (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Nagle Avenue (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Nassau Avenue (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - New Street (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - New Chambers Street (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Norfolk Street (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - North Moore Street (Trinity Church Farm) (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - North William Street (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Oak Street (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Old Slip (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Oliver Street (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Orchard Street (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Park Avenue (North to 42nd Street) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Park Avenue (42nd to 50th street) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Park Avenue (50th to 59th street) (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Park Avenue (59th to 72nd street) (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Park Avenue (72nd to 96th street) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Park Avenue (96th to 110th street) (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Park Row (1 out of 2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Park Row (2 out of 2) (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Park Street (formerly Cross) (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Park Terrace East (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Patchin Place (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Payson Avenue (Inwood) (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Pearl Street (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Peck Street (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Pell Street (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Perry Street (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Pike Street (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Pitt Street (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Pleasant Avenue [Harlem (Old)] (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Pomanders Walk (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Post Avenue (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Prince Street (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Printing House Square (See also: Park Row) (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Reade Street (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Rector Street (Box 24)
      - Renwick Street (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Republican Alley [or Manhattan Place] (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Ridge Street (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Riverside Drive (to 96th street) (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Riverside Drive (96th to 116th street) (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Riverside Drive (from 118th street) (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Riverside Drive (Shore R.R.) (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Riverview Terrace (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Rivington Street (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Roosevelt Street (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Rose Street [Colonial Prince Street] (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Rutgers Place (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Saint James Place (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Saint John's Place (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Saint Luke's Place (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Saint Mark's Place (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Saint Nicholas Avenue (formerly Harlem Lane) (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Saint Nicholas Place (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Seamen Avenue (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Sheridan Square (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - South Street (South Ferry to Coenties Slip) (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - South Street (Coenties Slip North to Fulton Street) (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - South Street (Fulton street to Roosevelt street) (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - South Street (Roosevelt street to Montgomery street) (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Spring Street (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Spruce Street (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Stanton Street (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Staple Street (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - State Street (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Stone Street (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Striker's Lane (now area from W. 52nd Streets between 11th & 12th Avenues) (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Stuyvesant Alley (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Stuyvesant Street (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Sullivan Street (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Sutton Place (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Sylvan Terrace (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Thames Street (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Thomas Street (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Thompkins Street (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Thompson Street (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Trinity Place (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Union Square East (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Union Square West (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - University Place (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Vandam Street (Trinity Church Farm) (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Vanderbilt Avenue (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Vandewater Street (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Varick Street (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Vesey Street (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Wadsworth Avenue (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Walker Street (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Wall Street (Cuts from "Wall Street in History") (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Wall Street (Broadway to William Street: 1 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Wall Street (Broadway to William Street: 2 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Wall Street (Broadway to William Street: 3 of 5) (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Wall Street (Broadway to William Street: 4 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Wall Street (Broadway to William Street: 5 of 5) (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Wall Street (William to East River) (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Warren Street (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Washington Mews (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Washington Place (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square East (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square North (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square South (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Washington Square West [part of MacDougal Street] (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Washington Street (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Water Street (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Watts Street (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Waverly Place (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Weehawken Street (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - West Broadway (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - West End (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - West Houston Street (formerly Hammersley street) (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - West Side Elevated Express Highway (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - West Street (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - White Street (Calkhook Farm) (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Whitehall Street (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - William Street (Hanover square to Maiden lane) (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - William Street (Maiden - Frankfort - Pearl street) (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Wooster Street (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Worth Street (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - York Avenue (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - York Street (Trinity Church Farm) (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - 1st Street (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - 2nd Street (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
      - East 3rd Street (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - West 3rd Street (formerly Amity Street) (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - East 4th Street (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - West 4th Street (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - 5th Street (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - 6th Street (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - 7th Street (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - 8th Street (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - 9th Street (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - East 10th Street (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - West 10th Street (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - East 11th Street (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - West 11th Street (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - East 12th Street (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - West 12th Street (formerly Troy Street) (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - East 13th Street (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - West 13th Street (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - East 14th Street (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - West 14th Street (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 15th Street (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - 16th Street (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - 17th Street (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - 18th Street (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - 19th Street (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - 20th Street (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - 21st Street (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - 22nd Street (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - East 23rd Street (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - West 23rd Street (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - 24th Street (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 25th Street (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 26th Street (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - 27th Street (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - 28th Street (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 29th Street (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 30th Street (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - 31st Street (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - 32nd Street (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - 33rd Street (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - East 34th Street (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - West 34th Street (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 35th Street (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 36th Street (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - East 37th Street (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - West 37th Street (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - 38th Street (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 39th Street (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - East 40th Street (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - West 40th Street (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 41st Street (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - 42nd Street Panorama (Both sides 3rd to 8th avenue) (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - East 42nd Street (Park Avenue - East River) (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - East 42nd Street (Grand Central) (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - East 42nd Street (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - West 42nd Street (5th to 6th avenue) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - West 42nd Street (6th to 8th avenue) (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - 43rd Street (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - 44th Street (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - 45th Street (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - 46th Street (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - 47th Street (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - 48th Street (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - East 49th Street (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - West 49th Street (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - 50th Street (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - East 51th Street (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - West 51th Street (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - East 52nd Street (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - West 52nd Street (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - East 53rd Street (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - West 53rd Street (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - East 54th Street (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - West 54th Street (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - 55th Street (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 56th Street (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - East 57th Street (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - West 57th Street (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 58th Street (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - East 59th Street (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - West 59th Street (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - East 60th Street (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - 61st Street (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - East 62nd Street (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - 63rd Street (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - 64th Street (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - 65th Street (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - 66th Street (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - 67th Street (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - 68th Street (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - 69th Street (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - 70th Street (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - 71st Street (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - East 72nd Street (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - West 72nd Street (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - 73rd Street (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 74th Street (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 75th Street (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - East 76th Street (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - West 76th Street (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - East 77th Street (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - West 77th Street (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - 78th and 79th Street (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - 79th Street (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - 80th Street (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - 81st Street (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - 82nd Street (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - 83rd Street (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - 84th Street (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - East 85th Street (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - 86th Street (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - 87th Street (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - 88th Street (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - 89th Street (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - 90th Street (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - West 91st Street (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - 92nd Street (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - 93rd Street (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - West 94th Street (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - 95th Street (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - 96th Street (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - East 97th Street (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - 98th Street (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - West 99th Street (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - West 100th Street (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 101st Street (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - West 103rd Street (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 104th Street (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - West 105th Street (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - 106th Street (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - West 107th Street (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - 108th Street (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 109th Street (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - West 110th Street (Cathedral Parkway) (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - West 111th Street (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 112th Street (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 113th Street (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 115th Street (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 116th Street (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - 117th Street (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 118th Street (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - 119th Street (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - 121th Street (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - West 122nd Street (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - 123rd Street (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - 124th Street (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - 125th Street (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - 126th Street (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - 127th Street (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - 128th Street (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - 129th Street (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - 130th - 131st - 132nd Street (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - West 133rd Street (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - West 134th Street (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - 135th Street (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - West 136th Street (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - West 137th Street (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - 138th Street (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - 139th Street (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - 140th - 149th Street (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - 150th - 159th Street (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - 160th - 169th Street (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - 170th - 179th Street (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - 180th - 189th Street (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - 190th - 199th Street (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - 200th - 209th Street (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - 210th - 219th Street (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - 220th - 228th Street (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - First Avenue (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Second Avenue (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Third Avenue (to 42nd street) (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Third Avenue (above 42nd street) (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Fourth Avenue (8th to 20th street) (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Fourth Avenue (21st to 26th street) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Fourth Avenue (27th to 30th street) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Fourth Avenue (30th to 33rd street) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Fifth Avenue (Washington Mews to 14th street) (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Fifth Avenue (14th to 19th street) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Fifth Avenue (21st to 23rd street) (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Fifth Avenue (24th to 26th street) (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Fifth Avenue (27th to 34th street) (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Fifth Avenue (34th to 40th street) (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Fifth Avenue (40th to 43rd street) (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Fifth Avenue (43rd to 45th street) (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Fifth Avenue (45th to 47th street) (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Fifth Avenue (47th to 50th street) (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Fifth Avenue (50th to 52nd street) (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Fifth Avenue (52nd to 54th street) (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Fifth Avenue (55th to 60th street) (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Fifth Avenue (60th to 72th street) (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Fifth Avenue (72th to 89th street) (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Fifth Avenue (90th - 143rd street) (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Sixth Avenue (to 32nd street) (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Sixth Avenue (32nd to 57th street) (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Seventh Avenue (11th street to 42nd street) (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Seventh Avenue (42nd street to 59th street) (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Seventh Avenue (from 110th street on) (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Eighth Avenue (Abingdon square to 31st street) (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Eighth Avenue (31st to 57th street) (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Eighth Avenue (110th street and up) (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Ninth Avenue (12th to 49th street) (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Tenth Avenue (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Eleventh Avenue (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Twelfth Avenue (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Thirteenth Avenue (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Avenue A (to 24th street) (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Avenue B (lower east side) (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Avenue C (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Avenue D (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Neighborhoods
      - Chinatown (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Five Points (Later Paradise Park) (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Greenwich Village (folder 1) (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Greenwich Village (folder 2) (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Harlem (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Inwood (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Lower East Side (folder 1) (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Lower East Side (folder 2) (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Manhattanville (folder 1) (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Manhattanville (folder 2) (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Stuyvesant Town (formerly Gashouse District) (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Washington Heights (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Greenwich Village (Balducci's) (Box 44a, Folder 1)
      - Greenwich Village (Building Gutted by fire) (Box 44a, Folder 2)
      - Greenwich Village (Interiors) (Box 44a, Folder 3)
      - Greenwich Village (Morton Street Dock) (Box 44a, Folder 4)
      - Greenwich Village (Store Windows) (Box 44a, Folder 5)
      - Greenwich Village (Street Scenes) (Box 44a, Folder 6)
      - Greenwich Village (Washington Square Park) (Box 44a, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Parks and Gardens
      - Battery Park (park views) (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Battery Park (views toward water) (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Battery Park (views toward water: aquarium) (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Battery Park (views toward water: with Castle Garden and before use as Aquarium) (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Battery Park (views toward park: general) (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Battery Park (views toward park: with Castle Garden) (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Bolton Garden (W. 158th street) (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Bowling Green (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Bryant Park (formerly Reservoir Square) (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Fort Fish and McGowan's Pass) (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Park Preparation) (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Central Park- pre-1860s views (Squatters' shacks) (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Maps (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Birds-eye views (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-General Views (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
      - Central Park-General Views with Animals (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Central Park-Winter views (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Central Park-Buildings-General Arsenal (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Arsenal including zoo (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Belvedere Castle (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Casino (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Mount St. Vincent (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Buildings-Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Central Park-Bridges-Bow Bridge (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Central Park-Bridges-Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Central Park-Fountains-Bethesda Fountain and Terrace (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Central Park-Fountains -Bethesda Fountain and Terrace (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds -The Lake (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds- Pond near 59th st. (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Lake and Ponds -Reservoir (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Central Park-The Mall (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - Central Park-Playgrounds (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Central Park-Roads-Transverse Road #2 at 79th street (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Central Park-Roads-Transverse Road #4 at 97th street (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Central Park-Statuary-Simon Bolivar Statue (Box 49, Folder 6)